let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"A software that allows a personal computer to pretend it, as a terminal is ",
		answer:"Terminal emulation",
		options:[
			"Terminal emulation",
			"Modem",
			"Bulletin board",
			"Auto-dialing"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"What frequency range is used for TV transmission and low power microwave applications?",
		answer:"Ultra high frequency : 300 MHz to 3000 MHz",
		options:[
			"Very low frequency : 3 kHz to 30 kHz",
			"Medium frequency : 300 kHz to 3 MHz",
			" Super high frequency : 3000 MHz to 30000 MHz",
			"Ultra high frequency : 300 MHz to 3000 MHz"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"Which of the following TCP/IP protocol is used for the file transfer with minimal capability and minimal overhead?",
		answer:"TFTP",
		options:[
			" TFTP",
			" TELNET",
			"FTP",
			"RARP"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"A half-duplex communication channel permits information to travel",
		answer:"Both ways, but not at once",
		options:[
			"At timed intervals",
			"One direction only",
			"Both ways, but not at once",
			"Both ways at once"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"Each IP packet must contain",
		answer:"Source and Destination address",
		options:[
			"Only source address",
			"Only destination address",
			"Source and Destination address",
			" Source or Destination address"
		
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"Which of the following port is used to connect device such as mouse, modem?",
		answer:"Serial port",
		options:[
			"Serial port",
			"Parallel port",
			"Firewire port",
			"Infrared port"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"What frequency range is used for micro-wave communications, satellite and radar?",
		answer:" Extremely high frequency : 30,000 MHz",
		options:[
			" Extremely high frequency : 30,000 MHz",
			"Super high frequency : 3000 MHz to 30000 MHz",
			"Medium frequency : 300 kHz to 3 MHz",
			"Low frequency : 30 KHz to 300 kHz"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"Which of the following has the smallest default maximum physical receive packet size?",
		answer:"Ethernet",
		options:[
			"Token Ring [4 Mbps]",
			"Token Ring [16 Mbps]",
			" ARC net",
			"Ethernet"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"One of the header fields in an IP datagram is the Time-to-live (TTL) field. Which of the following statements best explains the need for this field?",
		answer:"It can be used to prevent packet looping",
		options:[
			"It can be used to prevent packet looping",
			"It can be used to optimize throughput",
			"It can be used to reduce delays",
			"It can be used to prioritize packets"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Which of the following is not relevant to networking?",
		answer:"Bus hubs",
		options:[
			"Bus hubs",
			"Mesh network",
			"Stackable hubs",
			"Low-end stand alone hubs"
		]
	},
];